akselworks.com 2016-06-17

# Powermemo

Privacy Policy and Register is maintained by Akselworks Oy (later “Akselworks” or “Administrator”), Hansaksenkaari 26, 01150 SÖDERKULLA, Finland. Contact person is Pekka Ylisirniö, pekka.ylisirnio@akselworks.com.

Personal data collected by Akselworks is used to manage and maintain the relationship between Akselworks and clients, as well as for research and development. Akselworks may also share and publish aggregated, non-personally identifiable statistical information. Akselworks may disclose data at Akselworks on-line services for the other users of the same account. Data may be used for client communications and direct marketing if client has given permission to this.

Akselworks will only transfer personal data to third parties where the third party (a) has provided satisfactory assurances to Akselworks that it will protect the information consistently with Akselworks’ requirements or (b) is located in the EU or a country considered "adequate" for privacy by the European Commission, or (c) has certified to the Safe Harbor, and is accordingly independently responsible for complying with the Safe Harbor requirements.

Register contains Akselworks’ clients’ name, contact and other information which are provided to Akselworks in connection with the purchase or usage of the services.

Data is maintained for the period of client relationship and after relationship for as long as it is necessary for the purposes described in this privacy statement.

All administrators and other users of the Register have personal access granted by the Administrator (user ID, password and access level). Client personal information may only be accessed by persons who need to know such information for performing their duties.

Client is entitled to review client’s own personal data, demand correction of erroneous data and to deny usage of his/her data for direct marketing and also otherwise right to claim any right available for the client under applicable personal data legislation. Any requests must be sent to contact person of the Register.

The Powermemo.com website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Powermemo.com web site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

You can opt out of receiving targeted advertising at DAA opt-out site [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the NAI opt-out site at <http://networkadvertising.org/choices>, or if You live in Europe, the EDAA opt out site at [http://youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/).

This privacy policy is available online under [http://www.powermemo.com](http://www.powermemo.com/)
